today is the eighty-nine
I told you I had 1 important thing to say
and I won't roll you up
this shed here guy
you think
if i set up a marketing agency here
so i can put my sofas
my stuff
meet people
and there I can work with my tribe
so i kept thinking and said bro
more caraca
but if I have an operation like that
limit myself here physically
ah I don't know
for me the stop has to shine
the eye is on
and then I
and my second business idea
it's down here
my idea is
well at least it was making a partnership offer
you call this place
but there's the detail
let me show you
and this convenience here was going to be really nice man
because it gives a big movement
it's a cool post
it was going to be very interesting
then i was thinking
because i get stuck in operational
trying to see people management work in marketing
I don't know if that would limit me
could be a very good possibility
but still missing some details in my head
and then if I choose wrong
I'm the one who's going to have to hold this piano and not you
bro but let's continue this chat later
because I need
do 1 thing with that pile of money there
more
the merry christmas souvenir for you
tamo together face
little gift for you
tamo together
focus with of you
until tomorrow